* Follow Us

Menu

* Follow Us

* Journal
* Topics
* Issues

Menu

* Journal
* Topics
* Issues

Search  Search

Privacy Policy
--------------

### Table of Contents

Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry recognizes the importance of protecting the information of registered users of this website, and make all actions to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Disclaimer

The Website: The Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry is provided by ARBU Academic Publishing, having its main place of at Yenisehir Mh. Kardesler Cd. No: 7/2 Sivas, Türkiye.

**BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS DISCLAIMER AND OUR ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY**, as outlined below. If you do not agree to the terms of this Disclaimer and/or online Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use this Website or any of its content. The Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry is the copyright owner or licensee of the content and/or information on the Website, unless otherwise indicated. Individual documents in the Website may be subject to additional terms indicated in those documents.

#### Personal information

When you use this Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, organization, institution, postal address, email address. We may also collect other information, including, but not limited to, the URL you came from, IP address, your browser type, country, and telephone area code, where your computer is located and the pages of our Website that you viewed.

Your Personal Information will remain active until you request us to no longer send you communications. Should you submit information through our online forms, the data may be captured using various 3rd parties, including but not limited to Google Forms, Microsoft Forms, etc and then copied to the Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry ‘s data systems.

#### Acceptance of terms

By using this Website or submitting information to us; (a) you agree to accept the data protection practices outlined in this Privacy Policy; (b) you give consent to our collecting and processing your Personal Information in connection with the sale and distribution of our products and services; (c) you give consent to use of your information; (d) you agree that we may use the information that you provide or that we collect for the following purposes: (i) to register you with this Website, to set up and manage you’re the Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry account; (ii) to provide any services or information you have requested; (iii) to ensure that content from this Website is presented in the most effective manner for you; (iv)  to enforce our terms and conditions of use, including carrying out security reviews to validate your identity, contact details, and financial information; or in any other way as described to you at the time of collection of your Personal Information.

If you do not want us to contact you you may unsubscribe by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link on the email from the Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry or by contacting us directly at the [info@contemppediatrdent.org](mailto:info@contemppediatrdent.org).

#### Disclosure of your information

We may give information about you to the following, who may use it for the same purposes as set out above.

#### Access to and accuracy of your information

As a registered user, you can access your account information and make corrections or updates upon log in at any time. The accuracy of such information is solely the responsibility of the user. You may also request access to other Personal Information about you that may be held in the service. If you request to deactivate your account or delete your Personal Information, please email us at [info@contemppediatrdent.org](mailto:info@contemppediatrdent.org). 

#### Cookies

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered over the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your devices. They cannot be used to identify you on a personal level. If you do not accept cookies you will be unable to use this Website.

#### Information and disclaimers

We use reasonable care to ensure that the information appearing on this Website is up to date and accurate. While we take precautions to prevent the occurrence of errors and omissions, the user of this Website should not take the accuracy of the information for granted, but should check directly with us. None of the material contained in this Website is to be relied upon as a statement or representation of fact. 

#### External links

The Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry website contains links to other websites, which may or may not have connections to The Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry. Please note that The Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry is not responsible for the data protection practices of other websites.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry reserves the right to update, modify, and/or change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted here. If you continue to use this Website after we have changed this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to be bound by any such changes.

#### Security

We will protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access by using commercially reasonable security measures. If your Personal Information is accessed by an unauthorized third party, we will not be responsible for any direct or indirect damage caused as a result of such unauthorized access. Where we have given you a password which enables you to access certain parts of this Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.Unfortunately the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any data transmitted to this Website. Any transmission will be at your own risk.

#### Contact

All questions, comments, and requests regarding this Privacy Policy and/or your Personal Information should be addressed to Editorial Office, [info@contemppediatrdent.org](mailto:info@contemppediatrdent.org).

###### Article Categories

###### Resources

* Advertisers

###### About Us

* FAQs

###### Stay Connected

###### Follow Us

Copyright © Contemporary Pediatric Dentistry. All rights reserved.

Electronic ISSN 2757-5705.

Published by [ARBU Academic Publishing](http://www.arbuacademic.com/).
